Finding Aid for Netzorg family papers, late 1800s-2012.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Morton J. and Petra Fuld Netzorg papers
  - Correspondence
    - Baumgartner, Joseph, 1957-1984 (scattered) (Box 9)
    - Baur, Cyril, 1967 (Box 9)
    - Bay Area Civilian Ex-Prisoners-of-War, 1995 (Box 9)
    - Beam, Francis, 1971-1974 (with gaps) (Box 9)
    - Beaven, Sky with gaps, 1974-1997; 3 folders (Box 9)
    - Behr, Louise, 1984 (Box 9)
    - Belair, Charles, 1970-1978; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Bell, Kathleen, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Bellinger, Edith with gaps, 1948-1997; 5 folders (Box 9)
    - Bellows, Thomas, 1970 (Box 9)
    - Benda, Harry J. and Eva 1957-1975 with gaps and 1985, 1957-1985; 4 folders (Box 9)
    - Benson, Carolyn, 1952 (Box 9)
    - Bentley Historical Library, 1983 (Box 9)
    - Berger, Dr., 1973 (Box 9)
    - Berger, Kenneth, 1968; 1973 (Box 9)
    - Berkelouw, Isador, 1975-1981 (Box 9)
    - Berman, Rebecca, 1986-2001 (scattered) (Box 9)
    - Bernad, Miguel A. 1961-1996 with gaps and undated, 8 folders (Box 9)
    - Bernardo, Bernardo C., 1988 (Box 10)
    - Bernetein, H.H., 1959 (Box 10)
    - Beyer, William G., 1959; 1967 (Box 10)
    - Bibliographical Society of the Philippines, 1973-1976 (Box 10)
    - Biedzynski, James, 1986 (Box 10)
    - Bier, Gerd and Else, 1952; 1971-1985 (with gaps) (Box 10)
    - Black, James, 1976-1984 (Box 10)
    - Blackwell’s, 1971 (Box 10)
    - Blahd, Ruth Netzorg, 1959 (Box 10)
    - Blair, Philip, 1972 (Box 10)
    - Blumenthal, Joseph, 1949; 1965 (Box 10)
    - Bohannan, Charles T. R. and Dorothy, 1962-1987; 6 folders (Box 10)
    - Bohnam, Roscoe, 1968 (Box 10)
    - Boissere, Alex, 1979 (Box 10)
    - Bolasco, Karina, 1985-1986 (Box 10)
    - Bonin, Adelyn I. with gaps, 1947-1997; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Bookmark Inc., 1962; 1973 (Box 10)
    - Borman, Ruth, 1943-1947 (with gaps) (Box 10)
    - Bowker Company, 1965; 1972 (Box 10)
    - Bowler Banta, Mary and Banta, William, 1979-1990 (with gaps) (Box 10)
    - Bowler, J. E. and Dolores, 1944 (Box 10)
    - Boxer, Charles, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
    - Bradbury, Connie, 1980 (Box 10)
    - Brailey, Lester G., 1972-1982 (with gaps) (Box 10)
    - Brainard, Cecilia Manguerra (Box 10)
    - Bramble family 1940-1941, 1946-1986 with gaps, 1940-1986; 7 folders (Box 10)
    - Breitfeld, Alfred, 1975-1976 (Box 10)
    - Bresnahan, Roger, 1980-2001 (scattered) (Box 10)
    - Bressi, Arthur, 1971-1972; 1977 (Box 10)
    - Brimo, John, 1973 (Box 10)
    - Briscoe, Leonor, 1975 (Box 10)
    - Bromfield, David and Mary, 1939-1949; 1990s-2001 (scattered); undated; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Brosius, George and Peter, 1974-1975 (Box 10)
    - Brown, Charles, 1974 (Box 10)
    - Brown, Helen S. and William, 1977-1987 (with gaps) (Box 10)
    - Bryan, Edwin H., 1970-1978 (with gaps) (Box 10)
    - Bryant, Charles, 1977-1985 (with gaps) (Box 10)
    - Buchanan, Keith, 1966 (Box 10)
    - Bumpus, Larry, undated (Box 10)
    - Bunzel, Lawrence, Father, 1978-1986 (scattered) (Box 10)
    - Burdett, Thomas F., 1977; 1985-1987 (Box 10)
    - Burns, Thomas and Marcia, 1972-1987 (with gaps) (Box 10)
    - Burton, John, 1969-1971 (Box 10)
    - Butler, Margaret, 1977-1978; 1984-1985 (Box 10)
    - Buyser, Floripinas C., 1982-1983 (Box 10)
    - Byron, Rebecca, 1990-1991; 1997 (Box 10)
    - Cadleon Press, 1971 (Box 10)
    - Cahill, Marcia, 1949-1962 (scattered) (Box 10)
    - Cahill, William, 1996 (Box 10)
    - Calderon, Ms., 1986 (Box 10)
    - Caldwell, Kenneth S., 1981 (Box 10)
    - California, University of, 1956-1981 (scattered) (Box 10)
    - Callanan, Connie, 1962-1964 (Box 10)
    - Campbell, Angus, 1987 (Box 10)
    - Campbell, Marie, 1966 (Box 10)
    - Canoy, Reuben, R., 1984 (Box 10)
    - Capelle, R., 1953 (Box 10)
    - Capstickdale, Lyonel, 1975 (Box 10)
    - Carden, John, 1981; 1986 (Box 10)
    - Carringer, Wayne, 1974-1979 (with gaps) (Box 10)
    - Carrion, Jean Zaruba, 1980-1981; 1985 (Box 10)
    - Carrol, John S., 1957-1973 (with gaps) (Box 10)
    - Carson, Arthur L., 1964-1980 (scattered) (Box 10)
    - Carter, Thomas M. with gaps, 1980-1996; 5 folders (Box 10)
    - Carunungan, Celso, 1956-1969 (scattered) (Box 11)
    - Cascade House, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Case, Harry L., 1971 (Box 11)
    - Casey, Thomas, 1977-1978 (Box 11)
    - Caspari, David, 1975-1984 (with gaps) (Box 11)
    - Caspari, Peter and Erika, 1944-1996 (scattered) (Box 11)
    - Casper, Linda Ty and Leonard, 1964-1971 (with gaps); 1980-1984 (with gaps); 2002 (Box 11)
    - Cass Technical High School, 1961 (Box 11)
    - Catholic Trade School, 1969-1970 (Box 11)
    - Chandler, Karen and Curt, 1975-1985 (with gaps) (Box 11)
    - Chapman, Jack, 1987-1988 (Box 11)
    - Chapman, James W., 1956 (Box 11)
    - Charlton, Alberta, 1951-1952 (Box 11)
    - Chase, William C., 1976-1977 (Box 11)
    - Christenson, Laura, 1962-1984 (scattered) (Box 11)
    - Civian, J. L., 1943-1945 (Box 11)
    - Claes, Ethel, 1956-1973 (scattered) (Box 11)
    - Claiborne, Craig, 1965-1966 (Box 11)
    - Clark, Sherm and Susan, 1979-1988 (scattered) (Box 11)
    - Clemente, Wilfredo II, 1971-1972 (Box 11)
    - Clifford, Nicholas R., 1970 (Box 11)
    - Clores, Patricia, 1976-1977 (Box 11)
    - Clough, Margaret and Russell, 1976-1983 (scattered) (Box 11)
    - Cohl, Michael L., 1986 (Box 11)
    - Cole, Cannon, 1974 (Box 11)
    - Collins, Anthony, 1986 (Box 11)
    - Collamer, Mr., 1986 (Box 11)
    - Comley, Joseph, 1979 (Box 11)
    - Conklin, Harold C., 1956-1987 (with gaps) (Box 11)
    - Conley Books, 1972 (Box 11)
    - Conner, Electra A., 1978-1987 (with gaps) (Box 11)
    - Consumer Alliance of Michigan, 1971-1975 (scattered) (Box 11)
    - Consumer Union, 1948-1952 (with gaps); 1975 (Box 11)
    - Conyers, John Jr., 1974-1984 (scattered) (Box 11)
    - Cook, Marjorie, 1977; 1979 (Box 11)
    - Cooper, Helen Marie, 1978 (Box 11)
    - Cornell University, 1968-1975 (scattered); 1988 (Box 11)
    - Cornman, Ronald, 1962 (Box 11)
    - Covill, Erna B., 1982 (Box 11)
    - Covit, Bernard and Sara, 1966-1978 (with gaps) (Box 11)
    - Cox, Francis Lamar, 1962-1964; 1968 (Box 11)
    - Crabtree, Mary, 1977-1990 (scattered); undated (Box 11)
    - Craighead family, 1975-1982 (scattered); undated (Box 11)
    - Crane, Robert, 1961-1962; 1966 (Box 11)
    - Crane, Thomas A., 1975 (Box 11)
    - Cruikshank, Bruce, 1977-2002 (with gaps) (Box 11)
    - Cruz, Isagani R., 1985 (Box 11)
    - Cryster, Robert I., 1983-1986 (Box 11)
    - Cullinane, Michael, 1978-2001 (with gaps) (Box 11)
    - Current Book House, 1971-1972; 1974 (Box 11)
    - Currey, Cecil B., 1987 (Box 11)
    - Cushner, Nicholas P., Father, 1972; 1976 (Box 11)
    - Czajkowski, Florence and Peter, 1967-1978 (scattered); undated (Box 11)
    - Dablio, Marianita, 1985 (Box 11)
    - Dain, Harvey and Beatrice with gaps, 1943-1987; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Dalhart, Glenn A., 1985 (Box 11)
    - Daniels, Gordon, 1986 (Box 11)
    - Danielsson, Bengt, 1961-1965 (scattered); 1986 (Box 11)
    - Dansalon College, 1971 (Box 11)
    - Danto, Art and Shirley, 1948-1955 (with gaps) (Box 11)
    - Danziger, Kurt, 1951 (Box 11)
    - Darling, Frank C., 1972-1973 (Box 11)
    - David, Dennis M. V., 1982-1983 (Box 11)
    - Davidson, Nelle C., 1980 (Box 11)
    - Davis, Bonnie, 1997-2002 (scattered) (Box 11)
    - Davis, Joe Lee, 1948 (Box 11)
    - Daws, Gavan, 1985; 1987-1988 (Box 11)
    - De Alcurz, 1986 (Box 11)
    - Dealing, James, 1971 (Box 11)
    - DeBenko, Eugene, 1966-1985 (scattered) (Box 11)
    - DeCoursey, Rita, 2001-2002 (Box 11)
    - De Jaagdt, Peter, 1978 (Box 11)
    - De Jesus, Mr., undated (Box 11)
    - De La Costa, H., 1967; 1976 (Box 11)
    - Del Carmen, Rolando V., 1973 (Box 11)
    - Del Monte Ladies Civic Assistance Club, 1985 (Box 11)
    - Del Rosario, 1970; 1982 (Box 11)
    - Dellota, Mr. and Mrs., 1976 (Box 11)
    - Deloitte Haskins & Sells, 1986 (Box 11)
    - De Marco, Dorothy, 1987; undated (Box 11)
    - De Mayo, J. B., 1973 (Box 11)
    - Demetrio, Francisco R., 1971-1973 (Box 11)
    - Deming, W. Edward, 1947-1948 (Box 11)
    - Denver Art Museum, 1975 (Box 11)
    - De Selms, Charles C., 1943-1951 (scattered) (Box 11)
    - Dessewffy, Eva, 1971-1973 (Box 11)
    - Detroit, City of, 1961-1982 (scattered) (Box 11)
    - Detroit Free Press, 1970s (Box 11)
    - Detroit Friends Meeting House, 1950 (Box 11)
    - Detroit Public Library, 1959 (Box 11)
    - Detroit Public TV, 1981 (Box 11)
    - Dickens, Louis, 1986 (Box 11)
    - Diehl, Katharine Smith with gaps, 1966-1987; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Dienst, Eva, 1963 (Box 11)
    - Dobin, William and Jean, 1957 (Box 11)
    - Dodson, Osborne, 1976-1984 (with gaps); undated (Box 11)
    - Doeppers, Daniel F., 1968-1985 (with gaps) (Box 11)
    - Dombey, Mary, 1950 (Box 11)
    - Domeran, Alice, 1958 (Box 11)
    - Domke, Eva, 1969-1982 (scattered) (Box 11)
    - Domnauer, Margret and Ronald with gaps, 1943-1996; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Dorfman, David, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Dorman, William, 1959 (Box 11)
    - Dorson, Richard, 1962-1963 (Box 11)
    - Doty, Edouard R. L., 1971 (Box 11)
    - Dougall, Lucy, 1978 (Box 11)
    - Driggs, Frank, 1980 (Box 11)
    - Drummond, Stewart M., 1963 (Box 11)
    - Dulay, Peter Jr. and Heidi, 1962 (Box 11)
    - Dumanop, Antonio P., 1985-1989; 1995-1996 (Box 11)
    - Dunlap, William A. Jr., 1966 (Box 11)
    - Dunn, Cynthia, 1982; 1985-1987 (Box 11)
    - Duwa, Zenaida, 1983-1984; 1987 (Box 11)
    - Dyen, Isidore, 1970 (Box 11)
    - Earlham College, 1966-scattered1971 (Box 11)
    - Earthwatch, 1982; 1986 (Box 11)
    - Easthagen, Margaret, 1979; 1982 (Box 11)
    - Echols, John with gaps, 1962-1982; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Edades, Victorio C. and Jean, 1960-1963 (with gaps); 1976-1986 (Box 11)
    - Edades, Jean, 1998 (Box 11)
    - Edwards, Violet, 1955-1983 (scattered) (Box 12)
    - Eggan, Fred, 1957-1974 (scattered) (Box 12)
    - Eismann, Elsbeth, 1944 (Box 12)
    - Eisner, Helen, 1947 (Box 12)
    - Ellis, George A., 1975 (Box 12)
    - Ely, Richard and Mary, 1963-1972 (scattered) (Box 12)
    - Engel, Rene, 1965-1966 (Box 12)
    - Ennis, Jean, 1954-1961 (scattered) (Box 12)
    - Enterprise Publications, 1972 (Box 12)
    - Ephraim, Frank, 2002 (Box 12)
    - Eppnik, Alice, 1946; 1980; undated (Box 12)
    - Ernst & Ernst, 1961-1982 (scattered) (Box 12)
    - Escoto, Salvador P., 1971; 1973 (Box 12)
    - Ethridge, James M., 1972; 1980 (Box 12)
    - Eulau, Kurt, 1947-1950 (Box 12)
    - Everybody’s Bookstore, 1973 (Box 12)
    - Ewart, Robert M., 1951; 1980-1986 (with gaps) (Box 12)
    - Fabella Maximo P., 1977-1978 (Box 12)
    - Faerber, Max and Rae, 1961-1975 (scattered) (Box 12)
    - Falek, Rae, 1978-1986 (scattered) (Box 12)
    - Fan mail, 1948-1975 (scattered) (Box 12)
    - Faxon, Jack, 1975; 1978-1979 (Box 12)
    - Featherstone, Harry, 1978-1986 (scattered) (Box 12)
    - Feistel, Hartmut-Ortwin, 1976-2001 (scattered) (Box 12)
    - Felix, Alfonso Jr., 1980-1987; 1990-1991; 5 folders (Box 12)
    - Fellowship of Faith for Muslims, 1975 (Box 12)
    - Fennel, L. H., 1967 (Box 12)
    - Fergloute, Jacques, 1970; 1974 (Box 12)
    - Ferguson, Donald, 1950-1983 (scattered) (Box 12)
    - Fernandez, Doreen G., 1979-2002 (with gaps) (Box 12)
    - Ferrier, J. W., 1946 (Box 12)
    - Feustel, Mary J. and Henry, 1971-1987 (with gaps) (Box 12)
    - Fiegenbaum, David, 1975; 1980 (Box 12)
    - Field, Louis, 1985 (Box 12)
    - Fifield, Russell H., 1985 (Box 12)
    - Filipinas Foundation, 1982 (Box 12)
    - Filipiniana Book Guild, 1967-1968 (Box 12)
    - Filipino American, 1963 (Box 12)
    - Filipino Foundation, 1982 (Box 12)
    - Filipino Students Catholic Asociation, 1962 (Box 12)
    - Filipino Youth Activities of Seattle, 1971 (Box 12)
    - Firth, Robert H., 1980; 1986 (Box 12)
    - Fischer, Martin, 1946-1967 (with gaps) (Box 12)
    - Fisher, Rex, 1961 (Box 12)
    - Fisk, Nevin and Bernice, 1949-1965 (scattered); 1984 (Box 12)
    - Flat River Historical Society, 1973-1976 (Box 12)
    - Flory, John and Elizabeth, 1966-1988 (scattered) (Box 12)
    - Focus: HOPE, 1982 (Box 12)
    - Foley, Jack, 1978; 1987 (Box 12)
    - Fontanella, Claude and Kiaran, 1970s; undated (Box 12)
    - Foote, Nelson, 1948-1950; 1952-1953 (Box 12)
    - Ford Foundation, 1957 (Box 12)
    - Foronda, Marcelino A., 1969-1982 (scattered) (Box 12)
    - Frake, Charles C., 1958-1965 (scattered); 1975 (Box 12)
    - Frank, J. Russell, 1990 (Box 12)
    - Frederickson, Jane, 1986-1987; 1995 (Box 12)
    - Freedman, Michael P., 1986 (Box 12)
    - Frieder, Alexander, 1946 (Box 12)
    - Frieder, Tae S., 1945 (Box 12)
    - Friedlander, Rose, 1967-1984 (with gaps) (Box 12)
    - Friend, Theodore with gaps, 1960-1987; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Friends of Philippine Libraries, 1986 (Box 12)
    - Frey, Ernest J. and Winifred, 1960-1986 (with gaps) (Box 12)
    - Fromm, Margot, 1962-1965 (Box 12)
    - Fruto, Ligaya, 1978-1980 (Box 12)
    - Furst, J. L., 1985 (Box 12)
    - Gal, Sari, 1997-1998 (Box 12)
    - Gallin, Bernard, 1962-1963 (Box 12)
    - Galura, Hilaria B., 1987-1988 (Box 12)
    - Garcia, Irene G., 1975 (Box 12)
    - Garcia, Mauro, 1956-1970; 1981-1982 (Box 12)
    - Gardner, Frederick R. with gaps, 1952-1986; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Garilao, Ernesto, 1969 (Box 12)
    - Garland, Amanda, 1990 (Box 12)
    - Garney, Bernard, 1957-1958 (Box 12)
    - Garrett, Eugene A., 1989-1990 (Box 12)
    - Gastillo, Hugo B., 1956; 1974-1986 (scattered) (Box 12)
    - Gaynes, Ernest M., 1949-1957 (with gaps); 1970s (scattered) (Box 12)
    - Gelfand, May Ebihara, 1962 (Box 12)
    - General Motors Corp., 1971-1972 (Box 12)
    - Gerard, Fred, 1979 (Box 12)
    - Ghana Publishing Corporation, 1974 (Box 12)
    - Ghosh, Marianne, 1943-1958 (scattered) (Box 12)
    - Gianakos, Perry E., 1966-1986 (scattered) (Box 12)
    - Gibbon, Robert and Lolita, 1977; 1979 (Box 12)
    - Gibbs Bookshop, 1951-1952 (Box 12)
    - Gilbreth, Sarah, 1976 (Box 12)
    - Gillette, Carl, 1978 (Box 12)
    - Gitre, A., 1977 (Box 12)
    - Glaser, Edwin L., 1972 (Box 12)
    - Gleek, Lewis, 1979-1991 (Box 12)
    - Glendale Community College, 1975 (Box 12)
    - Goertzel, Mildred and Victor, 1950-1990 (scattered) (Box 12)
    - Goethals, Peter R., 1967 (Box 12)
    - Goforth, Vestal, 1963 (Box 12)
    - Golay, Frank H. scattered, 1957-1984; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Goldenberg, Michael, 1956-1960 (Box 12)
    - Golding, Robert F., 1966; 1975 (Box 12)
    - Goldstein, Harriet, 1944 (Box 12)
    - Gonzalez, J. with gaps, 1964-1984; 3 folders (Box 12)
    - Gonzalez, N. V. M., 1975-1979; 1981-1982 (Box 12)
    - Goodman, Grant, 1964-1983 (scattered) (Box 13)
    - Gopal, Baradas, 1970; 1974-1976 (Box 13)
    - Gosling, Peter, 1962 (Box 13)
    - Goss, Goerge L., 1962; 1964 (Box 13)
    - Gould, Randall and Agnes, 1965-1981; 10 folders (Box 13)
    - Gowing, Peter G., 1964-1983 (scattered) (Box 13)
    - Grattan, Harley C., 1965 (Box 13)
    - Graves, Ralph, 1986; 1990 (Box 13)
    - Green, Justin, 1978-1983 (with gaps) (Box 13)
    - Green, Larry and Laura, 1970-1974 (scattered) (Box 13)
    - Greenberg, Mark, 1962-1981 (with gaps) (Box 13)
    - Greenwood Press, 1969-1970; 1973 (Box 13)
    - Grevemeyer, Ernie and Nancy, 1949 (Box 13)
    - Griffin, Robert P., 1949 (Box 13)
    - Griffiths, Martha W., 1967-1972 (Box 13)
    - Grimble, R.J., 1975 (Box 13)
    - Gromball, Alwine, 1947-1948; 1962-1972 (scattered) (Box 13)
    - Growe, Lynn, 1986-1988 (Box 13)
    - Gruber, Ruth, 1952 (Box 13)
    - Gruenzner, Norman, 1974 (Box 13)
    - Guam, University of, 1962-1971 (scattered) (Box 13)
    - Guerrero, Wilfrido Ma., 1957 (Box 13)
    - Guthrie, George M., 1961-1970 (scattered) (Box 13)
    - Hadler, Jeffrey, 2001 (Box 13)
    - Hackett, Allen K. and Florence, 1962-1990 (with gaps) (Box 13)
    - Hacking, Robert, 1975-1984 (scattered) (Box 13)
    - Hahn, Emily, 1978-1990 (with gaps) (Box 13)
    - Haines, S. G., 1974 (Box 13)
    - Haire, Carl J., 1975 (Box 13)
    - Halas family, 1980-2006; 4 folders (Box 13)
    - Halbrecht, Herbert, 1982 (Box 13)
    - Hall, William C., 1971-1972 (Box 13)
    - Hallam family, 1949-1992; 15 folders (Box 13)
    - Halpern, Joel, 1964-1968 (scattered) (Box 14)
    - Halsema, James J. with gaps, 1947-2003; 10 folders (Box 14)
    - Halsema, Jane, 1980-1988 (with gaps) (Box 14)
    - Hamady, Susan, 1978-1979 (Box 14)
    - Handelsman, Norman R., 1978 (Box 14)
    - Hanson, Lee C., 1981 (Box 14)
    - Harding, Beatrice L., 1974-1975 (Box 14)
    - Hargrove, Thomas R., 1980; 1986-1990 (Box 14)
    - Haring, Douglas G., 1971 (Box 14)
    - Harper, Sylvia, 1978; 1981-1984 (Box 14)
    - Harrison, Cecilia, 1995 (Box 14)
    - Harrison, Thomas, 1961-1967 (scattered) (Box 14)
    - Hart, Donn V., 1957-1983; 9 folders (Box 14)
    - Hart, Harriett, 1984-1988 (Box 14)
    - Hart, Philip A. and Janey, 1966-1974 (scattered) (Box 14)
    - Hartendorp, A. V. H., 1953-1975 (scattered) (Box 14)
    - Haselkorn, Barbara, 1955-1965 (scattered) (Box 14)
    - Hawaii, University of, 1969-1975; 1986 (Box 14)
    - Hayden, Joseph R., 1957-1974 (scattered) (Box 14)
    - Hayes, Richard S., 1975 (Box 14)
    - Heider, Fred and Caroline, 1969-1990 (scattered); undated (Box 14)
    - Heine-Geldern, Robert, 1964 (Box 14)
    - Heinemann Educational Books, 1974-1975 (Box 14)
    - Hemenway, Jo, 1979 (Box 14)
    - Henderson, Erwin, 1986 (Box 14)
    - Hendry, Robert, 1955-1956 (Box 14)
    - Herold, C. William, 1986; 1990 (Box 14)
    - Herrmann, George and Marion, 1951-1985 (scattered) (Box 14)
    - Hess, Greta, 1956; 1966-1985 (with gaps) (Box 14)
    - Hessenberg, Ben, 1939; 1941 (Box 14)
    - Hester, E. D., 1957-1964 (with gaps) (Box 14)
    - Hester, Weldon B., 1985-1990 (with gaps) (Box 14)
    - Heyum, Renee, 1976-1986 (scattered) (Box 14)
    - Hezel, Francis X., 1970-1986 (scattered) (Box 14)
    - Hicks, Marguerite, 1970; 1986 (Box 14)
    - Higgins, Frank B., 1979-1983; 1986 (Box 14)
    - Highley, Mona P., 1980 (Box 14)
    - Hilke, Toni, 1947-1957; 5 folders (Box 14)
    - Hill, Art, 1979-1988 (scattered) (Box 14)
    - Hill, Frank, 1969 (Box 14)
    - Hill, Ruth Cobb, 1972-1974 (Box 14)
    - Hillard, Ed and Gretchen, 1978-1997 (with gaps) (Box 14)
    - Hinsdale, M., 1946; 1948 (Box 15)
    - Historical Conservation Society (Manila), 1973-1974 (Box 15)
    - Hoag, Paul, 1951 (Box 15)
    - Hollis, Gela, 1996 (Box 15)
    - Hollis, Joseph, 1967; 1976; 1996 (Box 15)
    - Hong Kong Archeological Society (Box 15)
    - Hong Kong, University of, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
    - Hopkins, Robert S., 1966 (Box 15)
    - Hornbostel, Gertrude and Earl, 1958-1986 (scattered) (Box 15)
    - Houston, Charles O. with gaps, 1954-2000; 8 folders (Box 15)
    - Howell, Mary J., 1971 (Box 15)
    - Hufana, Alex G., 1981-1985 (Box 15)
    - Huke, Robert E., 1965-1966 (Box 15)
    - Hulswit, William H., 1951-1969 (scattered) (Box 15)
    - Humanities Press, 1975 (Box 15)
    - Humphrey, Dolores, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Hunt, Chester 1956-1966, 1977-1986 with gaps, 1956-1986; 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Hunt, Joseph and Marilyn, 1970-2001 (scattered) (Box 15)
    - Hunt, Ray C., 1942-1946; 1983-1987 (Box 15)
    - Hurst, William, 1978-1979 (Box 15)
    - Hutterer, Karl, 1977 (Box 15)
    - India Book Hoise, 1973 (Box 15)
    - Indiana University Press, 1972 (Box 15)
    - Information Media Guaranty Program, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Ingle, Donald F., 1974-1975 (Box 15)
    - Institute of International Relations (China), 1975 (Box 15)
    - Institute of Southeast Asian Studies (Singapore), 1973 (Box 15)
    - International Institute of Metropolitan Detroit, 1977 (Box 15)
    - Iowa State University, 1969 (Box 15)
    - Ireland, Irma T., 1960 (Box 15)
    - Irikura, James K., 1960; 1966 (Box 15)
    - Irvine, Elizabeth, 1978-1979; 1985-1986 (Box 15)
    - Ives, Geraldine, 1976; 1986 (Box 15)
    - Jackson, Kennell Jr., 1975 (Box 15)
    - Jacobs, Eugene C., 1978; 1985 (Box 15)
    - James, Thelma, 1965-1978 (scattered); undated (Box 15)
    - Janson, Dorothy, 1986-1996 (with gaps) (Box 15)
    - Janson, Robert, 1975-1976; 1984; 1986 (Box 15)
    - Jessel, Eva, 1943-1951 (with gaps) (Box 15)
    - Jewish Community Center of Metropolitan Detroit, 1973-1976; undated (Box 15)
    - Jewish Home for Aged, Detroit, 1976 (Box 15)
    - Jo, Yung-Hwan, 1975 (Box 15)
    - Johnson, Jill, 1979 (Box 15)
    - Johnson, Robert, 1980 (Box 15)
    - Johnston, Emile G., 1963 (Box 15)
    - Jones, Jack F., 1980; 1985 (Box 15)
    - Jones, Jill, 1979 (Box 15)
    - Jones, Nancy and Wellington, 1974-1984 (scattered) (Box 15)
    - Jones, Robert R., 1970 (Box 15)
    - Jordan, Sydney, 1954; 1956-1957 (Box 15)
    - Jorgensen, Bonney R., 1996 (Box 15)
    - Jose, F. Sionil, 1965-1984 (with gaps) (Box 15)
    - Jose, Ricardo T., 1978-1997 (scattered) (Box 15)
    - Journal of American Folklore, 1965 (Box 15)
    - Journal of Asian Studies, 1962 (Box 15)
    - Jung, Paul T., 1968 (Box 15)
    - Jurney, Dorothy, 1975-1985 (with gaps) (Box 15)
    - Juvinall, Florence, 1981 (Box 15)
    - Kerr, James and Rose, 1945; 1948 (Box 15)
    - Kezer, Shirley H., 1990 (Box 15)
    - Kneller, Heni and Samuel, 1990-2003 (with gaps) (Box 15)
    - Kneller, Rolf and Anne 1943-1945, 1993-2003 with gaps, 1943-2003; 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Koenig, Fred W., 1987 (Box 15)
    - Krohn, Charles, 1987 (Box 15)
    - Kruck, Jean, 1991 (Box 15)
    - Lande, Carl, 1990 (Box 15)
    - Lederer, William and Ethel with gaps, 1943-1986; 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Legarda, Ben and Lita with gaps, 1957-1987; 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Levin, Carl, 1990 (Box 15)
    - Lewis, Douglas, 1997; 2000 (Box 15)
    - Liberia Antiquaria, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Lichtig, Edwin and Edna, 1990; 1997 (Box 15)
    - Lieberman, Trudy, 1970 (Box 15)
    - Lim, Paul Stephen, 1983-1984 (Box 15)
    - Lindemann, Klaus, 1984-1985; 1996 (Box 15)
    - Lindsey, Charles W., 1984-1986 (Box 15)
    - Linowitz, Shirley, 1987 (Box 15)
    - Lippmann family, 1975-1976; 1985 (Box 15)
    - Livraria Castro e Silva, 1971 (Box 15)
    - Longridge Military Books, 1979 (Box 15)
    - Lopez, Oscar and Eugenio, 1959-1960; 1963; 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Lopez, Salvador P. with gaps, 1947-1985; 3 folders (Box 15)
    - Lowenherz, Max G., 1983-1986 (Box 15)
    - Lowenstein, Arthur J., 1943-1947 (Box 15)
    - MacDonald, Glenn, 1982-1991 (with gaps) (Box 16)
    - Maddela, Inocencio B., 1985 (Box 16)
    - Magsaysay, Ramon, 1956 (Box 16)
    - Mahonar Book Service, 1971 (Box 16)
    - Maidenburg, Michael, 1969 (Box 16)
    - Mailaender, Irene, 1966-1985 (scattered) (Box 16)
    - Majul, Cesar Adib, 1958-1987 (with gaps) (Box 16)
    - Malay, Armando J., 1980-1986 (scattered) (Box 16)
    - Malaysian-American Chamber of Commerce, 1964-1967 (Box 16)
    - Malkin, Sol and Mary Ann, 1949-1986 (with gaps) (Box 16)
    - Manfield, Helena, 1946-1959; undated (Box 16)
    - Mangahas, Federico, 1970-1978; 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Mangahas, Ruby, 1979-1987 (Box 16)
    - Manila Bureau of Public Libraries, 1963 (Box 16)
    - Manning, John L., 1971-1986 (scattered) (Box 16)
    - Manson, Sara, 1981 (Box 16)
    - Manuel, E. Arsenio, 1956-1978 (with gaps) (Box 16)
    - Marcus, Jacob R., 1960-1961 (Box 16)
    - Marquardt, Fritz with gaps, 1967-1986; 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Marquardt, Josephine, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Marquez, Eli J., 1974 (Box 16)
    - Marshall, Byron, 1970-1996 (scattered) (Box 16)
    - Marshall, Ruth, 1982-1986 (with gaps) (Box 16)
    - Marshalls Island High School, 1968-1974 (scattered) (Box 16)
    - Martin, Charlotte Hagans, 1980-1981 (Box 16)
    - Martinez Cuesta, Angel, 1969-1986 (scattered) (Box 16)
    - Mason, L. W., 1968 (Box 16)
    - Massapequa Public Library and Schools, 1952-1966 (scattered) (Box 16)
    - Maude, H. E., 1958 (Box 16)
    - Maung Maung, 1959-1965 (Box 16)
    - May, Glenn A., 1981-1987 (scattered) (Box 16)